本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
■
翻译：阿好  王小麦  卫老哥  茶炒栗子
你被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
■
翻译：灰灰是菇凉  惠子  面条打包子  天朝直属
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
■
时间轴：阿包  凭陵新月  兜兜兜爹
我会知道  因为它是我造的
I know because...I built it.
■
后期：灰灰是菇凉   校对&总监： 阿好
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror,
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府认为这些罪行是无关信息
crimes the government considered irrelevant.
他们不肯作为  所以我决定插手
They wouldn't act, so I decided I would.
但我需要一个搭档
But I needed a partner.
救命
Help!
救命啊
Somebody help me!
拜托
Please!
我锁定了麦克纳布女士的位置
I'm locked onto Ms. Mcnabb's position.
她在两条街外的D大道往北逃
She's two blocks from you being pursued north on avenue "D."
你在吗
Are you there?
她现在从第五大道往西逃  跑往
Now she's moving west on fifth street heading toward-
天啊
Oh, dear.
你在哪儿  来不及了
Where are you? There's no more time!
你得做点什么
You have to do something!
不
No.
拜托
Please!
别紧张  芬奇
Relax, Finch.
我到了
I'm here.
哈利安全了
Haley's safe.
你是谁
Who are you?
良善守护者
Protector of the innocent.
听说你需要点守护
Heard you could use some protecting.
你那位腐败上司不希望
Your embezzling boss didn't like the idea
你出庭指证他
of you testifying against him in court,
所以就派这小丑来解决你
so sent this joker to make sure it didn't happen.
狄林杰先生
Mr. Dillinger,
他不是派了两名杀手追杀麦克纳布女士吗
didn't he send two hit men after Ms. Mcnabb?
这是最后一个  我保证
Last one, I promise.
希望行凶者需要救护车
I hope the threats required an ambulance,
而非验尸官
and not a coroner.
真不敢相信  你救了我的命
I can't believe that you saved my life.
不值一提
Don't mention it.
你刚才大受惊吓
You've had a very traumatic experience.
现在最好别一个人待着
You probably shouldn't be on your own right now.
不知道你怎么样  哈利  我蛮想喝一杯
I don't know about you, Haley, but I could use a drink.
今天周六  芬奇
It's Saturday, Finch.
号码不等人  狄林杰先生
The numbers never stop coming, Mr. Dillinger.
我想我一早就告诉过你了
I believe I told you that up front.
人总得偶尔休息一下
Guy could use a little r&r once in a while.
你不考虑多找个人轮班吗
You ever think about getting someone else in the rotation?
就你这班了
You are the rotation.
该去工作了
And it's time to get to work.
还有  狄林杰先生
Oh, and Mr. Dillinger,
下次再有漂亮女人
the next time an attractive woman wants
感谢你的救命之恩
to thank you for saving her life,
回句"不客气"就行了
a simple "You're welcome" should suffice.
谁啊
Who was that?
老板
My boss.
要我加班
Needs me to put in some overtime.
感谢你救我于危难之中
Thanks for getting me out of trouble.
感谢你身陷于危难之中
Thanks for getting into trouble.
你成天一个人待在这儿可不好  哈罗德
It's not good for you to be in here all day by yourself, Harold.
你不考虑养条狗么
You ever think about getting a dog?
谢谢  不过我不喝咖啡
Thank you, but I'm afraid I don't drink coffee.
不  这是茶  黑茶
No, it's tea--black chai.
你爱喝这玩意儿  是吧
That is your poison, right?
我喝的是煎绿茶
It's sencha green, actually.
差不多了
Close enough.
我可就知道你的名字
Seeing as how the only thing I know about you is your name--
还不是真名
which isn't really your name.
狄林杰先生  关于我  你只需要知道
All you need to know about me, Mr. Dillinger,
我雇你是为了阻止坏事发生
is that I pay you to stop bad things before they happen.
现在可以开始了吗
Now, are we ready to get started?
你付钱就行
Long as the checks clear.
丹尼尔・凯西
Daniel Casey.
亚利桑那州图森市人
Born and raised in Tucson, Arizona.
曾就读加州理工计算机科学专业
He got into Cal Poly's computer science program,
但在毕业前一年辍学了
but dropped out a year before graduating.
你非得这样吗
Must you do that?
你喜欢吗
You like this?
我叫她"格里塔"
I call her "Greta."
黑水公司的礼物
Blackwater souvenir.
她就差能帮我做饭了
If only she'd cook me dinner.
凯西有点孤僻  没家人可联系
Casey's somewhat of a loner. No family to speak of.
自由受雇于全国各大"虎队"
He freelances with various Tiger Teams around the country.
真像名字听起来这么有趣吗
Is that as exciting as it sounds?
公司会雇佣"虎队"
Companies use Tiger Teams
测试自身安全系统的漏洞
to test their security systems for weaknesses,
这点可以通过黑入自身系统达成
which they can find by hacking in themselves.
答案是无趣啊
So the answer's no.
凯西这些年侵入过很多公司
Casey's infiltrated numerous companies over the years.
也许他看了什么不该看的
Perhaps he saw something that he wasn't supposed to see.
或者偷了什么不该偷的
Or stole something he wasn't supposed to.
两个月前
Two months ago,
凯西取消了他的电话和有线电视
Casey canceled his phone and cable subscriptions,
之后就再也没动过银行账户
and he hasn't made a single bank transaction since.
我不想这么说  芬奇  不过这家伙可能死了
I hate to say it, Finch, but this guy could be dead.
感谢阁下的乐观主义精神  狄林杰先生
I appreciate your optimism, Mr. Dillinger,
不过我确定他还活着
but I'm certain that he's alive
因为我收到了他的号码
because I've received his number.
噢对了  号码
Ah, yes, the numbers.
总有一天  你会告诉我
You know, one day, you're gonna have to tell me
你怎么搞到预言情报的
how you get your divine intel.
那我们要怎么找凯西
So how do we find Casey?
如果凯西先生身陷某种麻烦
If Mr. Casey's in some kind of trouble,
他可能会联系老朋友
he may attempt to contact old friends.
这是莱斯特・斯特里克兰
This is Lester Strickland.
凯西不时会为他工作
Casey worked for him upon occasion.
根据他的"连网"资料
According to his Connectroid profile,
S02E14中的互联网公司
斯特里克兰周六常在一家酒吧看赛马
Strickland spends Saturdays at a bar watching horse races.
也许应该从那里开始
That might be a place to start.
我像那种看赛马的人吗
Do I look like the equestrian type?
我相信你会有办法
I'm sure you'll figure something out.
伙计  来杯最好的拉格啤酒
Pal, give me your best Lager.
据说"我是斯巴达克斯"会赢  赔率十赔一
Word is "I am Spartacus" is favored to win ten to one.
最好是  我刚在它身上下了两千块
He better, I just dropped two Gs on him.
你比我胆大多了
You're a braver man than I.
敬"我是斯巴达克斯"
To "I am Spartacus."
我本来都不该在这儿
I shouldn't even be here right now.
老板没完没了  逼我周末加班
My boss is breaking my balls, making me work weekends.
得为自己活着  朋友
You ought to get into business for yourself, my friend.
甭听命于人
Answer to no one.
你干什么的
What's your trade?
-我做安全系统审核  -是吗
- I, uh, I audit security systems. - Yeah?
我认识个人也是做那行的
You know, I got a buddy of mine in that industry.
也许你们见过
Maybe you two have crossed paths.
他叫丹尼尔・凯西
His name's Daniel Casey.
狄林杰先生  你在干什么
Mr. Dillinger, what are you doing?
-凯西是吗  -是啊
- Casey, huh? - Yeah.
我们以前一起在加州理工上学
Yeah, we went to Cal Poly together way back when.
你认识他吗
So, you know him?
我不认识
I'm afraid not.
不过我哪天要是遇上他  会代你问好
But if I do run into him, I'll tell him you said hello.
你说你叫什么来着
What'd you say your name was?
我没说过
I didn't.
配对成功
承认吧  芬奇
Admit it, Finch.
我提起加州理工你挺吃惊吧
You were surprised when I brought up Cal Poly.
没想到我有听你说话  是吗
Didn't think I was listening, did you?
我更吃惊的是你直接提起凯西先生
I was more surprised by how direct you were regarding Mr. Casey.
有必要这么吓人吗
Is it necessary to be so intimidating?
我们要找到凯西  就得要斯特里克兰打电话给他
We don't get to Casey until Strickland calls him.
要他打电话  就得要吓吓他
He's not gonna do that unless he's spooked.
如果他打给凯西先生了  他肯定会告诉他
And if he calls Mr. Casey, no doubt he'll tell him
躲着你点
to steer clear of you.
如果你不喜欢我的风格
You don't like the way I do things,
欢迎你到一线亲自动手
you're more than welcome to come get dirty in the trenches.
如何
How 'bout that?
来了
And there we go.
克隆电话
莱斯特・斯特里克兰
喂
Hello?
丹尼尔  你到底惹上什么麻烦了
Daniel, what the hell did you get yourself into?
他们去找你了  是吗
They came to see you, didn't they?
是啊  有个野蛮人自称是你的老朋友
Yeah, some Neanderthal claiming to be an old pal of yours.
不只他一个
And he wasn't the only one.
大约一个小时前  两个人  一男一女
About an hour ago, some couple-- a man and a woman--
在咖啡店门口拦住了我
stopped me outside my coffee joint,
问我有没有见过你
asking if I'd seen you.
这辈子没这么受欢迎过
Never been so popular in my life.
会面之前我会躲起来
I'll stay scarce until the meeting.
好  明天我会把包裹准备好
All right, I'll have that package ready for you by tomorrow
以防万一
in case you need it.
谢了  莱斯特
Thanks, Lester.
我现在只有你一位朋友了
You're the only friend I have right now.
藏好了  小子
Keep your head down, kid.
你觉得那包裹是指什么
What do you think that package was?
斯特里克兰先生擅长伪造文件
Mr. Strickland's area of expertise is false documents.
也许他在帮凯西先生伪造假身份
It may be that he's creating a fake identity for Mr. Casey.
凯西在躲什么人
Casey's trying to hide from someone.
听起来斯特里卡兰提到的那两个人正在找他
Sounds like that couple Strickland mentioned might be after him.
而且他们领先了一步
And they have a head start.
是啊  不过他们可没有终结者芬奇
Yeah, but they don't have the Finch-inator on their side
施展黑客魔法
working his hacker mojo.
电话反向查询
斯特里克兰拨的号码是预付费手机
The number that strickland dialed is a prepaid cell phone.
>搜索中
只要我侵入其运营公司
If I can access the carrier that it belongs to,
应该就能查出GPS坐标
I may be able to elicit GPS coordinates.
你到底是从哪儿学的这套东西
Where the hell'd you learn to do all that stuff anyway?
我说过了  狄林杰先生
As I've said before, Mr. Dillinger,
我很注重隐私
I'm a very private person.
是啊
Yeah.
凯西先生的信号并未移动
Mr. Casey's signal still hasn't moved.
也许该进去酒店里边找他了
It may be time to start looking for him inside the hotel.
你该给我弄个服务生的身份
Should've getting me a job as a bellhop,
否则我不知道怎么找他
I don't know how I'll find him.
那你怎么就确定另一方
And how can you be sure that the other party
还没进去里边找他呢
hasn't already found him inside?
因为我在外边发现他们了
'cause I think I just made them outside.
斯特里克兰说是一男一女  是吗
Strickland said a man and a woman, right?
这个城市有八百万人
There are 8 million people in this city.
我们特工能闻出同类
The thing about operators, we can smell our own.
再说从我过来到现在  他们就没动过
Plus they haven't moved since I got here.
没错  相信我  芬奇
Yeah, trust me, Finch.
我找到威胁了
I just found our threat.
我把那两个人的照片发给你了  芬奇
I'm sending you a photo of the couple, Finch.
你不能做下什么在线面部识别吗
Can't you do some sort of facial matching thing online?
没你说得那么简单  狄林杰先生
It's not quite that simple, Mr. Dillinger.
不过不重要了
Though it may not matter.
那男人是中情局的
That man is CIA.
介意说下你怎么知道的吗
Mind telling me how you know that?
说来话长
It's a long story.
但凯西先生卷入的麻烦
But whatever trouble Mr. Casey's gotten into,
涉及美国政府
it involves the United States government.
我可以告诉你  那男人能力非凡
And what I can tell you about that man is he's highly efficient.
你确定他们没发现你吗
Are you sure they haven't made you as well?
拜托  芬奇  你雇我的钱不白花
Please, Finch. You hired me for a reason.
对我多点信心啊
Give me a little more credit than that.
也许我们早点完工
Maybe, if we finish early,
马克会让我们在城里多待一两天
Mark will let us stay in town an extra day or two.
你还能喜欢到洛克菲勒中心溜冰啊  卡拉
Never pictured you as a Rockefeller ice-skating type, Kara.
纽约的重要景点之一
我想的是
I was thinking more like...
圣诞接管毒品交易
take over the drug trade for Christmas,
新年一把火烧掉
burn it down by New Year's.
听起来真热闹
That sounds like a hell of a party.
你有什么计划吗
You got plans?
继续跟踪前女友吗
Going back to stalking the ex-girlfriend again?
我想的是[加勒比海]阿鲁巴岛
Thinking more like Aruba.
对于谋杀平民这种事
Something about killing a citizen
我需要去海滩放松一下
makes me wanna kick back on a beach.
欣赏你穿泳裤  姐还没做好心理准备
I'm not ready to see you in a speedo.
别把丹尼尔・凯西当平民
And don't consider Daniel Casey a citizen.
他盗窃国家机密时就放弃权利了
He waived that right when he stole state secrets.
还是要让我们带牙齿回去吗
They still want us to take his teeth?
死亡证明啊
Proof of death.
几颗臼齿就行了
Couple molars should do it.
DNA样本过机场安检时
DNA swab's a lot easier to get through airport security
可比一袋牙齿容易
than a whole bag full of teeth.
规矩又不是我定的
I don't make the rules.
我们在街对面似乎又有一个麻烦
It looks like we've got another problem across the street.
那个喝水的高个子吗
That tall drink of water?
我有无数种方法处理掉他
I got a Christmas list of ways to dispose of him.
他跟我们不是同类
He's not one of ours.
像是本地人  不是外国政府特工
Looks local, not foreign government.
要我猜  私人武装
My guess? Private military.
佣兵
Merc.
也许凯西雇了保镖
Maybe Casey hired some muscle.
应该先把他干掉吗
Think we should take him out first?
先留着他吧
Let's keep him in play.
看看他做什么
See what he does.
如果他惹麻烦  就把他跟凯西一起做掉
If he's a problem, we'll put him in the ground along with Casey.
我看到凯西了  芬奇
I got eyes on Casey, Finch,
但你的政府朋友抢先跟上他了
But your friends from the government have a jump on him.
你得在他们之前救出凯西  狄林杰先生
You need to get to Casey before they do, Mr. Dillinger.
我知道利害关系  谢了
I'm aware of the stakes, thank you.
他们不会在大街上动手的
They're not gonna ghost him on a public street.
人太多了
Way too many people.
当我没说
Scratch that.
他比我想得要疯狂
This guy might be crazier than I thought.
芬奇  他们似乎现在就要动手了
Finch, I think it's happening now.
错误警报
False alarm.
他只是在他身上放了个窃听器
Guy was just planting a bug on him.
凯西刚进了间咖啡厅
Casey just ducked into a cafe.
可能就是之前说的那个"会面"
Could be the meeting he was talking about.
那一男一女不见了
Lost sight of Ozzie and Harriet.
美国经典情景喜剧中的两位男女角色
他们在凯西先生身上放了窃听器
Since they have ears on Mr. Casey,
可能正在一个更有利的位置窃听
could be listening from a more advantageous position.
好吧  我现在的位置就挺好
Yeah, well, I'm in a pretty primo spot myself.
现在我们也能窃听了
And we now have ears of our own.
配对成功
丹尼尔・凯西
Daniel Casey?
红帽子  对吗
Red cap, right?
伊恩・班克斯  参情委
Ian Banks, SSCI.
我们通过电话  我能坐下吗
We spoke on the phone. May I sit?
参情委  芬奇
SSCI, Finch?
参议院情报委员会
Senate select committee on intelligence.
伊恩・班克斯可能是国会工作人员
Ian Banks may be a congressional staffer.
如果想举报涉及国家安全的犯罪
If you wanted to report a crime that pertained to national security,
就可以找参情委
SSCI would be one way to go.
之前的谈话说得太模糊
Our conversation was vague at best
所以现在我想更详细的了解
so right now I'd like to know a little bit more
你的所见所闻
about what you saw.
我的所见所闻
What I saw?
我没干过这个  所以先说清楚  好吗
I'm new at this, so help me out, okay?
你们要怎么保护我
How are you gonna protect me?
证人保护计划  把我送出国
Witness protection? Get me out of the country?
协议是怎样的
What's the-- what's the protocol?
我们有得当措施确保你的安全
We have measures in place to ensure your safety.
但需要时间
But they'll take time.
让一个人消失可不是易如反常的事
Making someone disappear isn't as easy as snapping your fingers.
对我向来容易
It is for me.
高中同学聚会都没有人会问问
I'm not exactly the guy everyone's gonna wonder about
我去哪儿了
at their high school reunion.
那组织最初选择我多半就是为这个
And probably why this group picked me in the first place.
要进行下一步
If we're to proceed,
你得告诉我更多关于那个组织的事
you'll need to tell me more about that group.
换位思考一下
Look at it from my position.
整天都有人向我们举报
We get calls all the time from folks reporting crimes
政府的罪行
committed by our government.
你有任何不法行为的证据吗
Do you have any proof of illegal activity?
你掌握了什么东西吗
Anything in your possession at all?
我需要保证
I need assurances.
好吗
Okay?
不论结果如何  不要把我扯进去
Whatever comes out on this, my name isn't anywhere near it.
确保这点  确保我的安全  否则我走人
Guarantee that and my safety or I walk.
匿名加安全  确保
Anonymity and safety, guaranteed.
但是首先  凯西先生
But for that to mean anything, Mr. Casey...
你得信任我
you have to trust me.
你说得对
You're right.
参情委几时创立的
When was the SSCI created?
-什么  -年份
- What? - The year.
告诉我  我们就一起走
Tell me that and we leave together.
芬奇  你有班克斯的照片吗
Finch, have you got a photo of Banks?
正发给你
Sending you one now.
这是伊恩・班克斯  那跟凯西说话的是谁
If this is Ian Banks, then who the hell is Casey talking to?
时间到
Time's up.
凯西先生  这不是
Mr. Casey, this isn't--
免谈了  好吗
Forget it, okay?
一切都感觉不对劲  你也不对劲
None of this feels right, you don't feel right.
你敢跟踪我  我一定会让你后悔
You follow me, I'll make sure you regret it.
不得不说  凯西的直觉很准
I'll say this for Casey, he's got good instincts.
他直接朝后门去了
He's making a beeline for the back exit.
可能直接撞到中情局的枪口上了
Which quite possibly leads into the arms of the CIA.
你得马上拦住他
You need to acquire him now.
等等
Wait!
凯西
Casey!
谢谢你
Thank you.
我还以为你会让我追着你跑
I thought for a second you were gonna make me chase you.
如此大吼大叫  太招人注意
Attracting a lot of attention, shouting like that.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是安保人员  这是我的客户
I'm security detail. This man's my client.
能跟我说说这是怎么回事吗
You mind telling me what this is all about?
-抱歉  我  -闭嘴  我在救你
- Excuse me, I-- - Shut up and let me save your life.
你真的应该把武器放在地上
You should really put your weapon on the ground.
凭什么呢
Why the hell would I do that?
首先  你刚刚把客户给丢了
For starters, you just lost possession of your client.
你们这些佣兵向来如此
You mercs are all the same.
从不会考虑周详
You never think things through.
狄林杰先生  你没事吧
Mr. Dillinger, are you all right?
好得很
Peachy.
有人来搅局了
Got a couple of party crashers
之前冒充伊恩・班克斯的那家伙领的人
led by the man formerly known as Ian Banks.
还剩一个货
One chump left.
有趣了
That got interesting.
凯西呢
Where's Casey?
上头可不会高兴了
Powers that be aren't gonna be happy.
上头说凯西是叛国者
Powers that be sold Casey as a traitor.
那他为什么想要和政府官员会面
So why was he meeting with someone he thought was government?
不知道
Don't know.
反正那家伙也不是政府官员
That guy wasn't government, though.
问他几个问题也无伤大雅
Can't hurt to ask him a few questions.
反正无伤我们
Can't hurt us, anyway.
我找到凯西了  芬奇
I've got Casey, Finch.
打算告诉我你怎么知道他俩是中情局的了吗
Now you wanna tell me how you knew those two were CIA?
现在重要的是查出为什么
All that matters now is figuring out why
凯西先生有危险及我们怎么能帮助他
Mr. Casey is in trouble and how we can help him.
-你在跟谁说话  -不关你的事
- Who are you talking to? - None of your business.
不如你告诉我
Why don't you start by telling me
你到底干了什么  惹火了那么多人
what you did that pissed so many people off?
不是吧  都这样了
Really? After all that?
没我你早死翘翘了
You'd be a chalk outline without me.
抱歉  只是
I'm sorry, it's just...
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are.
是吗
Yeah?
我可知道你是谁  丹尼
I know all about you, Danny.
大学辍学
College dropout.
没有家人  至少没有能帮你的家人
No family, at least none that can help you.
你孤身一人  无处可逃
You're alone with nowhere to run.
狄林杰先生  够了
Mr. Dillinger, that's enough.
你朋友可保不住你的命  我可以
The friends you got ain't keeping you alive! I am!
五秒内我就能把你扔回狼堆里
And in five seconds I'm throwing you back to the wolves
除非你告诉我  为什么我要冒生命危险
unless you tell me why I'm sticking my neck out
来救你的命
to save yours.
好好好
Okay, okay, okay.
两个月前
Two months ago,
我接到一通政府人员的来电
I got a call from someone in the government.
他们想让我检测他们一套秘密系统的漏洞
They wanted me to test a secret system of theirs for weaknesses.
他们把我带进一个地堡
They threw me in a bunker
太平洋西北部的什么地方
somewhere in the Pacific northwest.
那是我见过最先进  最复杂的系统
It was the most advanced, complex system I'd ever seen.
数周来我一直试图黑进那该死的机器  直到
For weeks, I tried breaking into this damn machine, until--
狄林杰先生
Mr. Dillinger!
带凯西先生离开大街  快
Get Mr. Casey off the streets! Immediately.
你为什么忽然这么紧张
What's got you spooked all of a sudden?
照我说的做
Do what I tell you!
把他带到你认为最安全的地方
Take him to the safest place you can think of,
让他待在那里
and keep him there!
走
Let's move.
狄林杰先生  你为凯西先生找到安全地方了吗
Mr. Dillinger, have you found a safe place for Mr. Casey?
可以这么说吧
You could say that.
不不不  你不能带他来这里
No, no, no, you can't bring him here.
你得带他去别的地方
You have to take him somewhere else.
史密斯夫妇能找到的地方吗
Somewhere Mr. and Mrs. Smith can find him?
绝不能让找他的那些人发现这个地方
The people looking for him cannot discover this location.
你晕头了吧  外面都开战了
Maybe you missed a few beats, but it's a war zone outside.
总之  你可以放松了
Anyway, you can untwist your shorts,
我确保没人跟踪我们
because I made sure nobody followed us.
你万分确定吗
Are you positive about that?
我得坐下
I need to sit down.
-我得  -给他把椅子
- I need... - Get our friend a chair.
真是个噩梦
This is like a nightmare.
我完全不明白
I don't understand any of it.
你们是谁
Who are you people?
你可以叫我哈罗德
You can call me Harold.
这是我的搭档  狄林杰先生
And this is my partner Mr. Dillinger.
虽然看起来可能不像  但我们是来帮你的
It may not seem like it, but we're here to help you.
要喝茶吗
Can I get you some tea?
之前  这工作不过是救救姑娘  银行家
Until now, this job has been nothing but damsels and bankers.
凯西身后可是有顶级政府杀手追杀
Casey has grade "A" government hit men after him.
你认识的杀手
Hit men you know.
我们对付的到底是什么  哈罗德
What the hell are we up against here, Harold?
我跟你一样全凭猜测
Your guess is as good as mine.
凯西冷静一点后  我会跟他谈的
I'll speak with Mr. Casey after he's calmed down a bit.
或许现在最重要的是你到外面去
Perhaps we'd all be best served by your going outside
巡视一下周边
and securing the perimeter
确保你没有被跟踪
to be certain that you weren't followed.
好吧  老板
You got it, boss.
纽约
华盛顿特区
打扰你了吗
Am I interrupting?
没有  女士
No ma'am.
或许你可以说明一下
Perhaps you could elaborate
为什么一次消除后患的秘密行动
on how a stealth operation to eliminate a liability
会演变成曼哈顿中心的一场枪战
turned into a gunfight in the middle of Manhattan.
我们不知道
We had no reason to suspect
还有他方知道了丹尼尔・凯西的事
another party knew about Daniel Casey.
你是说你被抓了个现行
You mean you got caught with your pants down.
现在凯西还有了保镖
And now Casey has a bodyguard?
现在  中情局还没收到情报
At this moment, the agency has no intel.
所以我们更应该内部解决
Another reason why we should have taken care of this in-house.
我们的队伍就快组好了
Our teams are nearly online.
中情局杀凯西是因为他们当他是叛国者
CIA kills Casey because they think he's a traitor.
北极光安然无恙
Northern Lights stays protected.
如果凯西能搞定他的工作
If Casey would have done his job
我们获得北极光的权限
and we had access to Northern Lights,
我们眨眼间就能找到他
we could find him in a heartbeat.
其实是找到任何人
Or anyone else, for that matter.
无意冒犯  女士
All due respect, ma'am.
我们当初要是别杀奈森・英格拉姆  事不至此
We might not be in this situation if we hadn't killed Nathan Ingram.
最能提供无阻碍权限者
Who better to provide unfettered access to the source
莫过于其建造者了
than the man who built it?
奈森・英格拉姆已经没有价值了
Nathan Ingram outlived his usefulness.
所以会被处理掉
And he was dealt with accordingly.
你可以把他当前车之鉴
You might consider him a cautionary tale.
不如让自己有用点
Why don't you make yourself useful?
明早前把这烂摊子处理好
Put this mess to bed by morning.
现在情况是这样
Here's the problem.
上司希望这事能尽快解决
My supervisor wants this wrapped up ASAP.
你不交代  我搭档就要插手
If you don't start talking, my partner will get involved.
你绝不会想在她吃饭时打扰她
You don't want to interrupt her while she's eating.
你们为谁工作
Who do you work for?
你们想从丹尼尔・凯西身上得到什么
And what do you want with Daniel Casey?
一个唱红脸  一个唱白脸
Good cop, bad cop?
别逗我笑了
Don't make me laugh.
我要是没被绑在椅子上
If I wasn't in this chair...
我会轻松折断你的脖子
I'd snap your neck like a twig.
警告过你了  老兄
Tried to warn you pal.
只有一个小小的问题
There's just one minor problem with that.
你就被绑在椅子上呢
You are in the chair.
老天  我爱死这玩意儿了
God, I love this stuff.
知道我最爱它哪一点吗
You know what I like the most?
总是欲罢不能
Can't get enough of it.
牛
Rad.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你的系统
Your setup.
我没见过像这样的Unix系统变种
I've never seen a Unix variant like that before.
-很牛  -谢谢
- It's rad. - Thank you.
但我没见到你的备用电源
But I don't see your battery backup.
如果电量耗尽了怎么办
What happens when the power goes out?
图书馆靠大楼周围的一些燃料发电机
The library is powered by a few gas generators
来进行供电
scattered around the building.
只要有燃料  灯就会一直亮着
As long as there's fuel, the lights stay on.
不在电网内
Off the grid.
看来我来对地方了
Looks like I came to the right place.
你似乎很了解电脑系统  凯西先生
You seem to know your way around systems pretty well, Mr. Casey.
我在图森长大
I grew up in Tucson.
总得找点事打发时间
You gotta do something to pass the time.
我从十岁开始写代码
I started coding when I was ten.
对于我来说  调试系统比跟人聊天容易得多
I could debug a system easier than carry a conversation.
我向来不擅与人交流
Guess I was never much of a people person.
你现在交流得很好啊
I'd say you're doing just fine for now.
不过我能理解你的意思
But I do know what you mean.
有时候人的确更为复杂
Sometimes people can be rather complicated.
而电脑只会按设计好的代码运行
A computer only does what you've programmed it to do.
没错
Exactly.
至少我之前是这么想的
At least that's what I used to think.
-这是什么  -我花了两个月钻研的东西
- What's that? - What I spent the last two months working on.
多半也是所有人都想杀我的原因
And probably why everyone's trying to kill me.
能透露下你之前
What can you tell me about the work you were doing
为政府做的工作吗
for the government?
开始只是普通的活儿
Started out as a normal job.
他们要我测试一些系统
Some system they wanted me to test.
安排我住进个旅馆
They put me up in a motel.
没有电话  没有电视  全天候有警卫
No phone, no TV, guards around the clock.
每次载我进出那机构都要蒙住眼
They'd drive me to and from the facility blindfolded.
我都不知道我在哪个州
I mean, I didn't even know what state I was in.
这就有点过分了
It seems a bit excessive.
那么保密
All that secrecy.
是啊  不过能见到那个系统就值得了
Yeah, it almost seemed worth it once I saw the system.
那是我前所未见的复杂设计
It was the most complicated layout I'd ever seen.
还有那些我所接触过的
Not to mention, the strongest heap of hardware
最强大的硬件设备
I've ever tried to breach.
不管我怎么做  它都不动如山
Nothing I threw at it made a dent.
这么说你未发现漏洞
So you were unable to find a weakness.
后来我发现基本输入输出系统接口上隐藏有东西
Not until I found something hidden in the BIOS interface.
一个后门
A backdoor.
让我直接进入了操作系统
took me straight into the operating system.
后门
A backdoor.
我进去了
I was in.
把一些零散代码复制到了电脑上
Managed to get a few bits of code onto the laptop
然后系统被唤醒了  开始反制
before the system woke up and bit me.
它自动适应了我的入侵  将我封锁在外
It adapted to my hack. Locked me out.
你拿到的那些代码
The code you pulled...
你知道是什么吗
any idea what it was?
太先进了  简直像是外星来的
It's so advanced it's almost alien.
我设法分离出了九位数代码中的一部分字串  但是
I've been able to isolate a few strings of nine-digit numbers, but...
含义不明
no clue what they mean.
那系统把你封锁在外后发生了什么
What happened after the system locked you out?
我总有一种感觉
I couldn't shake this feeling
好像我不是在测试那个系统
that I wasn't testing the system.
而是在告诉政府如何侵入它
I was showing the government how to break into it.
所以我告诉他们搞不定
So I told them I was finished,
多谢工作邀约
thanks for the gig.
然后我感觉脖子被针刺了
Then I felt a needle in my neck.
我晕了过去
And I blacked out.
我在一个汽车后备箱里醒来
I woke up in the trunk of a car,
口袋里装着一封遗书
with a suicide note in my pocket.
他们应该是打算杀了我
Figured they planned on killing me somewhere
布置成我自杀的样子
and making it look like I did it myself.
你是怎么逃脱的
How did you manage to escape?
那辆车时速开到了160公里
The car must have been going a hundred miles an hour
还是大雨天
in the driving rain.
发生了交通事故  很严重
There was an accident, bad.
我能逃出来
I got out of that car
是因为车撞进了一根柱子里
because it was wrapped around a pole.
前面的两个人都死了
Two guys in the front were dead.
我抓起我的包
I grabbed my bag,
从他们钱包里拿了点现金就逃了
took the cash in their wallets and ran.
还以为打给参情委就安全了  但是
Thought I'd be safe calling the SSCI, but...
结果都知道了
we know how that turned out.
这故事真令人难以置信  凯西先生
That's an incredible story, Mr. Casey.
难怪中情局要追杀你
It certainly explains why the CIA is after you.
不过  还有个问题
However, there is the question
今天早些时候与你见面的那个男人
of the man you met with earlier today.
那人大费周折地见你
That man went to a great deal of trouble to meet with you.
我们完全不知道他是谁  为谁工作
We have no idea who he is or who he works for.
但我肯定的是  你为政府做的秘密工作
But I think it's safe to say that the secret work you did
现在已不是秘密了
for the government is no longer secret.
晚上好  兰伯特先生
Good evening, Mr. Lambert.
看来你的酬金领取之路有了麻烦
Understand you had difficulty in acquiring our prize.
中情局的行动比我们预料得更激进
CIA acted more aggressively than we anticipated.
他们在光天化日出手抓凯西
They tried to render Casey in broad daylight.
他被他们抓住了吗
Is he in their custody now?
有人把他救走了
Someone pulled him out of there.
有私人保镖保护他
Private detail, watching his back.
不过中情局还是抓了我们一名特工
CIA did, however, capture one of our operatives.
他们现在肯定在逼问他我们的身份
They're no doubt pressing him now as to who we are.
我可以分出人手去找回他
I can divert resources to recover him.
我们的人能照顾自己
Our people can take care of themselves.
现在全世界只有一个人最有价值
Right now there's only one man on the planet of any value,
那就是丹尼尔・凯西
and that's Daniel Casey.
好的  先生
Very well, sir.
兰伯特先生
Mr. Lambert.
再让我失望  我会另找高明
Fail me again, and I'll find someone more adequate for the task.
听明白了吗
Are we clear on this?
是的  格里尔先生  谢谢
We are, Mr. Greer. Thank you.
这是香农和韦弗的原版
This is an original edition of Shannon and Weaver's
美国数学家
《通信的数学理论》
Mathematical Theory of Communication.
这太
This is...
我想你想说的词是"牛"
I believe the word you're looking for is "rad."
你在干什么
What are you doing with that?
你截获的小段代码
The fraction of code that you captured here
我看着略眼熟
is not entirely unfamiliar to me.
我试着微调一下
I was going to try to tweak it a bit.
好吧  小心点  好吗
All right, just be careful, okay?
唯一能阻止所有人杀我的就是这个
It's the only thing keeping everyone from killing me.
以及你
Besides you.
你说得对
You're right.
除了政府想要你死
In addition to the government wanting you dead,
还有第二相关方
there is also a second interested party,
我们对其一无所知
about whom we know nothing.
我在黑暗网络安排了出售
I've arranged for a sale on the darknet.
-你要交给他们  -不
- You're gonna give it to them? - No.
我总觉得这个组织在乎的
I have a hunch that the group's concern
是手提电脑  而不是拥有它的人
lies with the laptop and not the man carrying it.
如果我们卖了  他们可能会叫手下停止追杀你
If we sell it, they might call off their pursuit of you
专心找代码
in favor of finding the code.
那就解决了一组神经病
Takes care of one group of psychos,
但解决不了中情局啊
but doesn't really help us with the CIA.
是解决不了
No, it doesn't.
所以我的搭档正在租飞机
Which is why my partner is chartering a plane
送你安全出国
to fly you safely out of the country.
好吧  没有新身份我走不了多远
Yeah, I won't get too far without a new identity.
我有个朋友帮我做了身份文件
I had a buddy drawing up some papers for me as a "Hail Mary."
此时最好是避免接触任何已知联系人
Might be wise to avoid known associates at this time,
如果可以的话
if you can help it.
这次刚好就可以
And, in this case, you can.
我冒昧自行创造了一个新身份
I took the liberty of creating a new identity myself.
还有一部安全手机
Also a clean phone.
看来你都想周全了
Sounds like you thought of everything.
你逃多久了
So how long have you been running?
挺明显了  这个地方  你的设备
It's obvious. This place, your setup.
我认为你对那个代码的了解
And I think you know more about that code
远不止你所说
than you're willing to admit.
我知道与你研究过的这个系统
I know that anyone that has contact with this system
有关的人
that you worked on...
要么死了
either ends up dead...
要么失去太多  宁愿自己死了
or they lose so much, they wish they were.
事实上  除了狄林杰先生
The truth is, besides Mr. Dillinger,
你是唯一到过这儿的人
you're the only person that's ever been here.
我必须请求你
I have to ask you--
不  你不必
No, you don't.
哈罗德  我欠你一条命
Harold, I owe you my life.
不管结果如何  就算他们抓住我
However this shakes out, they catch me...
我也不会说出你和这个地方
I won't tell them anything about you or this place.
希望你还享受热身
I hope you enjoyed the warm-up.
因为接下来要开始铁人三项了
'cause we're about to run the triathlon.
第一项
First event...
"这头小猪"
"This little piggy."
第二项  我喜欢称之为
The second one I like to call...
"[玻璃]脆弱下巴"
"Glass jaw."
给你一个建议
Word of advice:
尽量别吞下去
Try not to swallow it.
第三项由你决定
I'll leave the third one up to you.
最好想想  哪个身体部位
It'd be helpful to think about which body part
你能舍弃
you could live without.
借一步
A word.
甜蜜的负担啊
Ol' ball and chain.
我去去就回
I'll be back.
我认出这表情了
I recognize that look.
准备告诉姑娘  不许人家玩儿了
You're about to tell a girl she can't have any fun.
我只是在等着
I'm just waiting for the part
这酷刑几时能帮我们找到凯西
where torturing this guy helps us find Casey.
我这才刚开始呢  给点时间
I'm just getting started. Give it time.
相信我  你那么威胁
Trust me, the way you're threatening him,
他要交待  现在已经交待了
If he was gonna spill, he'd of done it by now.
他会交待的  不管他说不说
He'll spill. Whether he talks or not.
这倒新鲜
That's new.
我们还不如几小时前杀了他
We should've killed him hours ago.
至少当时他朝我们开枪了
At least he took a shot at us.
我们甚至不知道凯西到底犯了什么罪
We don't even know what Casey's guilty of.
我要不是很了解你
If I didn't know you any better,
还以为你打算质疑命令
I'd say you were about to question orders.
不  我会再次抓到凯西
No. I'm gonna reacquire Casey.
然后我会杀了他
And then I'm gonna kill him.
准备好了吗  先生们
Ready, gentlemen?
一切都顺利吗  狄林杰先生
Everything all right, Mr. Dillinger?
再过几个小时
In a couple of hours
我们这位朋友就会飞往布拉格
our friend here's gonna be on a plane to Prague.
-煎绿茶  -谢谢
- Sencha Green. - Thank you.
我还需要一小时完成凯西先生的文件
I'll need just another hour to finish Mr. Casey's documents.
他一上飞机
Once he's in the air,
我需要你处理一件我们必须了结的事
I need to fill you in on some other business we have to conclude.
卖掉凯西的硬盘
Selling Casey's hardware.
我并没告诉过你
I hadn't told you that yet.
我知道
I know.
因为你非常注重隐私  哈罗德
Because you're a very private person, Harold.
你愿意的时候才肯分享
You only share things when it suits you.
对我可不公平
Not a very good deal for me.
再继续为你工作  我会死掉
Probably wind up dead if I keep working for you.
我不知道这小可爱里是什么
I don't know what's on this puppy,
但我知道很多人想得到它
but I know a lot of people want it.
所以我自己牵线找了买家
So I lined up a buyer of my own.
结果发现中国人特别有兴趣
Turns out the Chinese are more than a little curious
购买某些秘密科技
to get their hands on some secret technology.
狄林杰先生
Mr. Dillinger...
你干了什么
what have you done?
你雇我时就知道我是条鲨鱼
You knew I was a shark when you hired me.
所以当我闻血而动时就别吃惊了
Don't act surprised when I smell blood in the water.
住手  住
Stop, st--
根本就没安排飞机  对吗
There's no plane, is there?
有安排
There is.
为我准备的
It's just for me.
你要交出我吗
You gonna turn me in?
你觉得我鸟你的死活吗
Do I look like I give a damn about what happens to you?
你不如就做自己最拿手的
Why don't you do what you do best?
逃吧
Run.
喂
Hello?
莱斯特  是我
Lester, it's me!
-你还好吧  小子  -是的
- You all right, kid? - Yeah!
算是吧  不好
Kinda. No. Look,
看来我还是需要那些文件
turns out I'm gonna need those papers after all.
我刚整理好
I just got it all in order.
不如你来我办公室吧  我在这儿等你
Why don't you come by the office? I'll be here.
这样就轻松多了
Suppose that makes things easier.
你没必要伤害他
You don't have to hurt him.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
他不该死
He doesn't deserve to die.
海啸夷平了一整座印度村庄
A tsunami wipes out a village in India.
村民们都是好人  不该死
Those are good people who don't deserve to die.
你朋友是叛国者
Your friend is a traitor.
一切都是他罪有应得
And he's gonna get everything that's coming to him.
喂
Hello?
-凯西先生  你没事吧  -没事
- Mr. Casey, are you all right? - Yeah.
看来你的行动还是有纰漏
I'd say you still got a few glitches in your operation.
-你在哪儿  我去接你  -不用了
- Where are you? I'll come and get you. - No need.
去找莱斯特取文件  然后就此消失
Gonna get my papers from Lester and disappear.
不行  太危险了  拜托  凯西先生
No, it's too dangerous, please, Mr. Casey.
我仍然能帮你脱身
I can still get you out.
你为我做得够多了
You've done more than enough.
要不是你  我早就没命了
I'd be dead if it wasn't for you.
不用担心
And don't worry.
我不会给你寄明信片的
I won't send you a postcard.
转身
Turn around.
慢点
Slowly.
你没必要这么做
You don't have to do this.
当然有必要
Sure, I do.
丹尼尔・凯西可是国家公敌
Daniel Casey's an enemy of the State.
其罪当诛
A crime punishable by death.
你之前在跟谁讲电话
Who were you on the phone with?
不关你的事
None of your business.
你们这些人已经夺走我太多东西了
You people have taken enough from me.
休想再得到更多
You're not getting anything else.
看到凯西了吗  约翰
Any sign of Casey, John?
我已经找到他了
I've got eyes on him.
很好  这边就交给我吧
Good. I'll secure things here.
难怪人家说英雄所见略同啊
What is it they say about great minds?
你们来晚了  伙计们
Little slow to the party, fellas.
好戏散场了
Keg's tapped.
凯西在我们手上
We have Casey.
你能迟点再解决他吗
Would you consider a stay of execution?
我需要跟他独处一会儿
All I need is a little time alone with him.
你为什么要找这家伙
What's your deal with this guy?
我只想问他几个问题
I just want to ask him a few questions.
等我问完  他就完全归你们
When I'm done, he's official property of
中央情报局了
the Central Intelligence Agency.
大家各取所需
Everyone gets what they want.
我们都能活着离开
We all walk out of here alive.
抱歉  兄弟
Sorry, pal.
无论如何
For what it's worth,
你都不可能活着离开
you were never getting out of here alive.
凯拉
Kara?
我没事  约翰
I'm fine, John.
被几个自动找死的感染了
Caught a little grief from the suicide squad,
所以得回报一下
so I had to give it right back.
基本都干掉了
Killed most of them.
跑了一个
One got away.
需要几分钟清理下房间
Gonna need a few minutes to sanitize the room.
不
Oh, no.
凯西怎么样
What about Casey?
他还喘气吗
He still sucking air or what?
断气了
Not anymore.
我把他丢进河里去  车上会合
I'll dump him in the water and meet you at the car.
你得赶快离开这儿
We should get you out of here.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我直视过叛国者的双眼  凯西
I've looked into the eyes of traitors before, Casey.
你不是叛国者
You're no traitor.
你看来不过是惹上了麻烦
You just look like a man who's trapped.
你搭乘下一班大巴去缅因州
You're gonna take the next bus headed to Maine.
到了卡里布后
When you arrive in Caribou,
有人在等着开车送你去加拿大
a man will be waiting to drive you into Canada.
如果他告诉我你没出现
If he tells me you didn't show up,
我会亲自去找你
I'm gonna come looking for you.
等我找到你  心情可不会怎么好
And when I find you, I'm gonna be in a very bad mood.
听明白了吗
Do you understand me?
你帮我离开这儿  我保证就此消失
You get me outta here, I promise I disappear.
人间蒸发
Like a ghost.
很好
Good.
还有件事  凯西
One more thing, Casey.
上头需要有死亡证明
Boss is gonna need proof of death.
给我几颗臼齿就行
Couple of molars should do it.
介意自己动手吗
Care to do the honors?
搞定了吗
We clean?
搞定了
We're clean.
很好
Good.
收工了
We're done here.
凯西身上没有什么东西
Casey didn't have anything else on him.
他偷的东西仍旧流失在外
Whatever he stole is still out there.
与我们无关
Not our problem.
上头让我们放手
Powers that be said we're moving on.
不明原因  也不关心
Don't know why, don't care.
我们有新任务了
We've been reassigned.
去哪里
Where?
摩洛哥
Morocco.
天气预报气温21度  晴天
Forecast is 70 degrees and sunny.
微笑  约翰
Smile, John.
我们今晚可让世界更安全了
We just made the world a little safer tonight.
红钩
中央公园
狄林杰先生  等等
Mr. Dillinger, wait!
你是怎么找到我的
How the hell'd you find me?
追踪我的手机  是吗
Tracked my phone, didn't you?
当然了
Course you did.
你到底想要什么  哈罗德
What the hell do you want, Harold?
来阻止我  埋葬我  免得引火烧身吗
You here to stop me or bury me in case this backfires?
不能追溯到你头上  是吧
Can't have anything trace back to you--that it?
-你得相信我  -相信你
- You have to trust me. - Trust you.
我怎么相信你  你自己谁都不信
How can I trust you when you don't trust anyone?
如你所说  代码是血
It's like you said: the code is blood in the water,
但你不是唯一的鲨鱼
but you're not the only shark.
世界上的所有政府都会
There isn't a government on this planet
拼命想抢到手  他们已经行动了
that wouldn't kill to get it and they have,
狄林杰先生
Mr. Dillinger.
我就知道你知道这是什么
I knew you knew what this was.
跟你获得号码有关  是吧
It has something to do with how you get your numbers, doesn't it?
你要想告诉我  就现在
If you wanna fill me in, now's your chance.
我想也是
That's what I thought.
求你了  没必要这样
Please, it doesn't have to be this way.
这都是你造成的
You made it this way.
因为你什么都瞒着我
By keeping me in the dark.
他们会杀了你
They'll kill you.
谢谢给我这份工作  哈罗德
Thanks for the job, Harold.
别跟着我
Don't try to follow me.
昨晚怎么回事
What happened last night?
我们认为是凯西保镖的那个人
The man we thought to be Casey's bodyguard
企图将电脑卖给中国人
attempted to sell the laptop to the Chinese.
我们的特工赶到  处理了他
Our agent arrived and neutralized him.
然后处理了其他人
Then proceeded to dispatch several others.
但是出了点  麻烦
There was, however, a complication.
有一名买家带着电脑跑了
One buyer got away with the laptop.
这么说那特工失败了
So the agent failed.
她的任务报告中可不是那么写的
That's not how she put it in her debrief.
她说如果我们早点派她去
She said if we'd sent her sooner,
她本可统统杀光
She'd have killed them all.
她说什么
She said what?
坦白说  她的原话
To be honest, her exact words
要更加"丰富多彩"
were slightly more colorful than that.
总的来说
All things considered,
我认为可以对她委以重任
I think we can expect great things from her.
没人告诉过你
Didn't anyone ever tell you
晚上这公园不安全吗
it isn't safe to be in the park at night?
我们有电脑位置的线索了
We have a lead on the location of the laptop.
我们追踪买家到一处软件机构
The buyers were traced back to a software facility
位于中国鄂尔多斯
in Ordos, China.
这事儿惹的麻烦过多了
The thing's more trouble than it's worth.
那两名负责凯西的中情局特工
The two CIA agents on the Casey job--
害电脑流失出去的家伙
the ones that let the laptop get away in the first place--
让他们去确认设备
send them in to confirm it's the device.
然后摧毁它  连同他们一起
Then destroy it. Along with them.
不能冒险让此事反噬我们
We can't risk these things getting back to us.
必定完成  夫人
Consider it done, ma'am.
狄林杰先生  我
Mr. Dillinger, I...
音频拦截
凯西死了
Casey's dead.
但我追踪到电脑了  在中国鄂尔多斯
But I've managed to track his laptop to Ordos, China.
很高兴你能做出补救  兰伯特先生
Glad you could salvage something from this, Mr. Lambert.
追踪恶意软件
带队伍过去
Get a team together.
连接目标
丹尼尔・凯西  是吧
Daniel Casey, I presume?
你怎么知道那个名字的
How do you know that name?
我们有位共同的朋友
We have a mutual friend.
事实上  我正因此而来
In fact, that's why I've been sent here.
真可爱  你会需要的
Cute. You're gonna need that.
你卧室的地板下面
Underneath the floorboard in your bedroom,
藏有五万现金和一本假护照
you have $50,000 in cash and a fake passport.
去带上
I'm gonna need you to grab it.
-我们要去什么地方吗  -你要去
- Are we going somewhere? - You are.
哥伦比亚卡塔赫纳  你去找一位格林菲尔德先生
Cartagena, Colombia. You're looking for a man named Greenfield.
S03E06中被根救走的弟弟
可惜  我得去别处
Sadly, I've got other places to be.
虽然你是很漂亮
Look, you're really pretty and all,
但这没有道理
but this doesn't make any sense.
你只要知道
All you need to understand
现在有更高的使命在召唤你
is you have a higher calling now,
所以你该离开了
so it's time for you to leave.
还有  我来时可能吸引了一些注意力
Also, I may have attracted some attention on my way in here.
持枪者随时可能赶到
Men with guns should be arriving any second.
我一转那开关
When I turn that dial,
你就只剩下两分钟时间
you're gonna have about two minutes
然后这里就要爆炸了
before this place explodes.
你是怎么知道这一切的
How do you know all this?
如我所说
Like I said...
我们有位共同的朋友
we have a mutual friend.
现在  她需要你的帮助
And right now, she needs your help.